Guide to the Guinea-Bissau Collection
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Guinea-Bissau collection
1971-2000
MS 1521
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
0.52
(3 boxes)
The collection consists of printed material and ephemera relating to the political and social conditions in Guinea-Bissau.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Transferred from the African Collection Curator.
Associated Materials
African Collection, MS 605; African Postcard Collection, MS 1575; Pamphlet Collection, MS 1351. Manuscripts and Archives, Yale University Library.
Arrangement
The material in the original accession is arranged chronologically. Additions to the collection may vary in arrangement.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Scope and Contents
The collection consists of printed material and ephemera relating to the political and social conditions in Guinea-Bissau.
Children -- Guinea-Bissau; Women -- Guinea-Bissau; Guinea-Bissau -- Politics and government; Partido Africano da Independência da Guiné e Cabo Verde
- Inventory, 1971-1993, undated
  - Partido Africano da Independência da Guiné e Cabo Verde (PAIGC): printed material, 1971-1991, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Guinea-Bissau liberation: documents; journals; printed material, 1973-1993, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Government information pamphlets; brochures; booklets, 1988-1990 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Women's movement/organizations: journals; newsletters; printed material, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Government documents; journals; reports, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Additional Material, Undated; Accession 1995-M-146
  - Additional printed materials, Undated (Box 1)
- Additional material, 2000; Accession 2015-M-001
  - Printed material, pennants, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 1)